He was talking to Anne.
他那时正在和Anne谈话.
At first I thought he was so mean.
开始我认为他很差劲.
A real snob,you know?
是个真正的势利小人,你懂吗?
He is not,though.
然而他不是.
He said he barely got through school.
他说他勉勉强强上完小学和中学.
He told me he did really badly at university.
还告诉我他大学读的也不好.
Well,he learned to run a company somewhere.
Well, 他在某个地方学会了经营公司.
He makes a ton of money.
他赚很多钱.
That's the thing.
怪就怪在这里.
He said he was bad at maths.
他说他的数学不好.
At what?
什么不好?
Maths.
数学.
You mean math?
你是说math?
We say maths.
我们说maths.
You must mean all the different maths.
你一定是指各种不同的数学.
Because I mean the one basic math.
因为我指的是最基础的数学.
Whatever.
随便哪个都行.
But Wendy,listen to this.
但是Wendy, 听我说.
He told me making money is easy.
他告诉我赚钱很容易.
He said,"If I buy someting for one dollar,and sell it for two,
他说,"如果我用1美元买一件东西,然后以2美元卖出,
I make money from that one per cent difference."
我就从那百分之一的差价中赚钱."
One per cent?You mean a hundred per cent.
百分之一?你的意思是一百分之一百.
Right.The man can't figure a percentage to save his life.
对. 他就算是为了救命也搞不清楚百分比.
Tell me about it.
你说的没错.
You should see the tip he left me!
你该看看那他留给我的小费!